應該有這麼個世界
There's a world that should be real somewhere
缺少緊張，愛遍世間
There's a lack of tension and love to spare
真希望我曾經去過
I would tell you that I'd been before
它就在逐夢之門身後
It was just behind the dreamer's door
就在逐夢之門身後
Just behind the dreamer's door
如畫般的地和七彩般的天
Painted hills and colored skies
那兒的景色絕對會你驚豔
A wondrous view that simply strikes the heart
有人負責高掛滿天星
There's one who holds the stars in place
有人負責撐起整片天
Another who keeps it all from falling apart
每天走著一樣的規律
The same routine runs every day
但他們就是這樣
but that's just who they are
那堵牆外頭的生活
Life outside of the wall
只希望我曾經夢過
I could say I'd dreamed it
我只要一次，但老實說
real one time, if at all
我也很難說沒有過
I could hardly tell you
會認識誰，會見到什麼
Who's to know, what you'll find
我知道它就在那兒
But it's there, I'm sure
你想要的不過
What you're looking for is
就在逐夢之門身後
just behind the dreamer's door
有人總是工作到傍晚
There's one who works until sundown
有人總能看到你的美
Another who sees the beauty in everyone
他呀，把天空視為心肺
This one takes the sky to heart
這位則樂子永遠找不完
The other one knows the best ways to have fun
安靜的她雖還很迷茫
The quiet one's still searching but
她已找到她的志向
she knows who she'll become
那堵牆外頭的生活
Life outside of the wall
只希望我曾經夢過
I could say I'd dreamed it
我只要一次，但老實說
real one time, if at all
我也很難說沒有過
I could hardly tell you
會認識誰，會見到什麼
Who's to know, what you'll find
我知道它就在那兒
But it's there, I'm sure
你想要的不過
What you're looking for is
就在逐夢之門身後
just behind the dreamer's door
張開眼，自己看
Open up, take a look
你絕對不會相信
You will never believe it
向前進，迎著風
Take a step, feel the air
珍惜你眼前所見
Cherish what you see
有位女孩總想做到最好
There's a girl who wants to do her best
到完美前她都不會睡覺
'Til she has it, she won't stop or rest
不知道它會藏著什麼
Doesn't know just what there is in store
逐夢之門身後有什麼
What there is behind the dreamer's door
就在逐夢之門身後
Just behind the dreamer's door